During a meeting with Paul Manduka, chairman of the UK's Prudential Life Insurance Group,
Prime Minister Nguyen Xuan Phuc expressed his
hope that Prudential would
expand its business in Vietnam and implement
more practical and effective programs and projects to
positively contribute to enhancing the
competitiveness of the insurance and
financial services industry in Vietnam. Since last year, Prudential has
invested 500 billion VND to purchase
30-year government bonds, and the group has
also committed to increasing its total
investment in 30-year government bonds
to 6,000 billion VND. The Prime Minister is very interested
in Prudential's activities.